<resources>
    <string name="app_name">myGame</string>

    <string name="startMenu">
        Hello there stranger... You have entered a restricted app! Leave now or
        face and suffer the consequences! If you wish to ignore this warning
        hit the ENTER button and your wish shall be granted! Be Warned!
    </string>

    <string name="instructions">
        The door behind you has been locked and any attempt
        of escape will cost you your life. Outside these walls are hungry lions
        that have not eaten in years! Shall you choose to exit and manage to
        escape from the lions, then your life shall be spared and consider
        yourself lucky! You have the option to escape by heading back South,
        or would you like to continue by going North, East, or West? Within
        this haunted place is a safe exit, but most rooms are filled with traps.
        Choose where you go carefully!
    </string>

    <string name="choose">
        Choose Wisely!
    </string>

    <string name="direction">
        Which \nDirection?
    </string>

    <string name="wrong_direction">
        Wrong direction you stupid human! Select another direction! Because of such a stupid action, you
        have lost one life!
    </string>

    <string name="exit">
        Congratulations! You have called my bluff! You are now free to go and have successfully escaped
        with ease. You are lucky to have not faced all the obstacles. Now leave and never come back!
    </string>

    <string name="lobby">
        You are now in the lobby. Don\'t worry human, this is the only place where
        you are safe. If you see any paranormal creatures, just run back to the lobby and you shall
        be safe. You have the option to head NORTH, WEST, or EAST. Head SOUTH and face those ravenous
        lions! You have been warned!
    </string>

    <string name="basement">
        You have entered the basement. As you can see, the dead bodies that were here
        have all turned to ash. You have the option to stay here or go back and head SOUTH. Trying
        to go in a different direction will only cost you one life!
    </string>
</resources>

